<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0"> <channel>      <title>You need to know about Electric Toothbrush from the Electric Toothbrush manufacturer, supplier, wholesaler, distributor, and factory</title>        <description>To find and shop the best Electric Toothbrush, you need to know about the highest quality of Electric Toothbrush manufacturer, supplier, wholesaler and distributor from a factory in </description>          <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/</link>   <lastBuildDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 21:59:20 +0800</lastBuildDate>   <language></language>            <item>	     <title>Damascus Rose Mask</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_8vtp1614846114.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Beauty Secret Rose Mask&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Beauty Secret -Rose Silk-wing Mask choose the perfect Rose and use the fresh petal to reserve its original substance. Then, use the special ways that can control wind velocity, temperature and humidity Precisely. The purpose is that releasing something important inside the Rose. Peoney Mask can let you maintain your face skin simply and efficiently. Trying Peoney&amp;rsquo;s Facial Mask immediately and you will be satisfied with its effect. You also can find your skin will be changed better and better after you use Peoney Rose Mask. You don&amp;rsquo;t need to spend too much money and you can achieve the perfect state of your skin. There are too many great items that are good to you in Peoney Mask. Then, our Facial Mask use organic Rose that you can use it without a doubt. Because we persist using and choosing the natural item which we can find surrounding in our earth. Such as in the forest or some mountains. The place Rose can grow up safely and naturally. Because there don&amp;rsquo;t have any harmful thing in those places. The soil in those places are clean and pure. The plants which planting at there can maintain its pure and precious substance. Therefore, it is pretty difficult thing and precious product, our Peoney Mask made it.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/damascus-rose-mask.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Damascus Rose Mask</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_8vtp1614846114.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/damascus-rose-mask.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Damascus Rose Facial Mask</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_bip81614846120.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Beauty Secret Damascus Rose Mask&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Beauty Secret -Rose Silk-wing Mask choose Damascus rose, it is a high-quality variety recognized in the world. Contain more than dozens of effective ingredients, including hyaluronic acid, arbutin and lecithin. Active transmission technology has won awards from various countries, including Geneva, France, South Korea, Silicon Valley and Tokyo. Peoney Facial Mask awards are from different area countries,such as Europeans, America and Asia. The ingredient that Hyaluronic acid, also known as hyaluronic acid or uronic acid, exists in the connective tissue and dermis of the human body. It is a transparent gelatinous substance. Hyaluronic acid can absorb 500-1000 times of its own moisture and is recognized as the best moisturizing ingredient. As we age, collagen, hyaluronic acid, subcutaneous fat, and bone in the body will gradually be lost and displaced, and the skin will gradually develop wrinkles and loosen, and become old. Using hyaluronic acid to fill the lost tissues of the skin, people will look younger and more energetic. Therefore, we can understand what important Hyaluronic acid is. Our skin can not lack of this substance. Our Peoney Beauty Secret Rose Mask uses the above raw materials and patented technology to maintain your skin, so that your skin will be fully moisturized and moisturized directly to the bottom of your skin, and you will feel younger.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/damascus-rose-facial-mask.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Damascus Rose Facial Mask</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_bip81614846120.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/damascus-rose-facial-mask.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Rose Silk Wing Mask</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_phz91614846126.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Beauty Secret Rose Silk-wing Mask&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Beauty Secret -Rose Silk-wing Mask choose the perfect Rose and use the fresh petal to reserve its original substance. Then, use the special ways that can control wind velocity, temperature and humidity Precisely. The purpose is that releasing something important inside the Rose. Damascus rose, Rosaceae Rosa, native to Syria, passed in Central Europe during the Crusades, the 14th century began to widely cultivated in France, is currently in Damascus Rose Bulgarian rose varieties grown in the main, is the world recognized quality Rose varieties. Damascus rose is a deciduous and upright cluster shrub, with a strong trunk and upright clusters, and the general plant height is about 150cm. The leaves are gray-green with bristles on the flower stems; double-petaled flowers are blooming, and the edges of the petals are slightly lighter and have a silky texture. There are mainly three varieties of pale pink, pink and white, of which pale pink has the best quality. The flower shape is larger than that of ordinary roses. Among the several varieties often mentioned at present, the petals of the Pingyin rose are the largest, the Damascus rose is the second, the Chiba rose is the third, and the Kushui rose has the smallest petal. Our Peoney Rose Mask is made from Damascus rose fresh flower, after careful refinement, protection, extraction and production, it retains the activity of the rose flower, so that the skin can get the best effect after use.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/rose-silk-wing-mask.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Rose Silk Wing Mask</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_phz91614846126.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/rose-silk-wing-mask.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Rose Silk Wing Facial Mask</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_fu7r1614846131.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Rose Silk Wing Mask&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Beauty Secret -Rose Silk-wing Mask uses thin and transparent silk fiber, it is light and soft, without interlining, it can still spread the mask easily. Possess 10 times smaller particles than ordinary essences, allowing beauty to penetrate deeper into the skin. Efficient moisturizing, help reduce wrinkles, relieve redness, as long as 6 minutes of application, it can penetrate into the bottom of the skin, long-term use, improve skin texture, and return to young skin age. Why we need Peoney Facial Mask? This is because after the mask is applied to the facial skin, it will form a thin film on the surface of the skin to temporarily isolate the skin from the air. The moisture in the skin cannot evaporate due to the coverage of the mask and can continue to moisturize and moisturize the skin. As the temperature of the skin rises, the pores open, dirt and old cutin are easily discharged, and the purpose of absorbing the ingredients in the mask is also achieved. Therefore, the skin that has used the mask is always easy to make up the next day, and the skin is also special It looks very smooth. Above these reasons, we can understand why using Facial Mask is an important thing to our skin.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/rose-silk-wing-facial-mask.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Rose Silk Wing Facial Mask</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_fu7r1614846131.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/rose-silk-wing-facial-mask.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Herbal Toothpaste Charcoal</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_uqq21614846137.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney BOBI Bamboo Charcoal Toothpaste&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney BOBI Bamboo Charcoal Toothpaste made of Natural bamboo charcoal and probiotics that can let your mouth keeping fresh. Removing bad smelling and increasing great good bacteria. Have the fresh breath after you use Bamboo Charcoal Toothpaste. It has certain adsorption, humidity control and antibacterial abilities. It also has the effect of cleaning tooth dirt and can remove bacterial stains on the teeth and clean. It is the role of teeth and fresh breath. Bamboo charcoal toothpaste, as the name suggests, is a toothpaste with bamboo charcoal as the main ingredient. Different from the white toothpaste, the color is natural black due to the addition of bamboo charcoal. Bamboo charcoal is charcoal made from bamboo, which has the ability to absorb and adjust humidity, and can also release far infrared rays and negative oxygen ions. These ingredients contained in bamboo charcoal toothpaste are natural ingredients. Bamboo charcoal has super adsorption capacity, which can effectively remove tooth stains and eliminate bad breath; it also releases negative oxygen ions and far infrared rays to prevent various oral diseases. You need to have one and give a choice to your teeth.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/herbal-toothpaste-charcoal.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Herbal Toothpaste Charcoal</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_uqq21614846137.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/herbal-toothpaste-charcoal.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Charcoal Toothpaste</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_4fp51614846143.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Charcoal Toothpaste&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney BOBI Charcoal Toothpaste is made in Taiwan. Using natural bamboo charcoal grinding, Amino acid food grade foaming and food grade ingredients. If eating by mistake, it will not accumulate toxins. Strict quality control, safe use every day. Including Vitamin B to protect gums can prevent bleeding and Probiotics and xylitol to prevent tooth decay. Tooth decay refers to the decomposition of teeth due to bacterial activity. Common dental caries bacteria are gram-positive aerobic bacteria such as lactococcus garvieae and streptococcus mutans. After they metabolize sugars, they produce acidic substances that can corrode teeth. Dental caries will appear in different colors from yellow to black, and its symptoms include pain and difficulty eating. Complications include inflammation of the tissues around the teeth, tooth loss, and the formation of tooth abscesses. How to prevent tooth decay? When brushing your teeth, the toothpaste must stay on the surface of the teeth for at least 2 or 3 minutes to achieve the anti-cavity effect. If it is less than this time, the ingredients in the toothpaste will not achieve the effect of tooth protection.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/charcoal-toothpaste.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Charcoal Toothpaste</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_4fp51614846143.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/charcoal-toothpaste.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Herbal Charcoal Toothpaste</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_15lp1614846148.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Charcoal Toothpaste&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney BOBI Bamboo Charcoal Toothpaste uses natural herbal ingredients can prevent dental plaque. Your teeth will have never had numb, bad breath, red and swollen teeth. Helping you kill all of bacterial in your month. Letting you have the excellent, pretty and bright white teeth. Then, you can laughing out loud with your beautiful teeth generously. Why we have Bad breath? Because it does not develop the habit of cleaning teeth after meals. The food residue of each meal is left in the mouth. If it is not removed immediately, the protein will be decomposed by bacteria and will form a foul smell. It is worth mentioning that the surface of the tongue is quite rough, and the tongue papillae are often keratinized, causing unevenness, forming a hiding place for a mixture of bacteria, food residues and epithelial exfoliated cells. The tongue is also a source of bad breath, so you should brush your tongue when you brush your teeth. If you want to solve this problem you need to clean your teeth carefully and have the good habit to brush your teeth in the correct time. By the way, Peoney Bamboo Charcoal Toothpaste also contains vitamins to protect the gums and prevent bleeding.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/herbal-charcoal-toothpaste.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Herbal Charcoal Toothpaste</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_15lp1614846148.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/herbal-charcoal-toothpaste.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Bamboo Toothpaste</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_bqk71614846153.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Bamboo Toothpaste&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney BOBI Bamboo Charcoal Toothpaste including fragrance of Rose flowers that can reserve in your month a long time. Made in Taiwan, Strict quality control, safe use every day. Using food grade ingredients instead of chemistry medicine. Effectively prevent periodontal disease and greatly reduce dental plaque. The toothpaste contains the essence of roses, which will leave a faint floral fragrance in your mouth after brushing your teeth, and it is not spicy. Peoney Bobi Toothpaste is made in a good Taiwan ISO factory. ISO we called International Organization for Standardization. It is a global non-governmental organization and a very important organization in the field of international standardization. The purpose of ISO is to integrate the opinions of various countries and develop and formulate a set of international standards, that is, international standards. The effect of bamboo charcoal products emphasizes deodorization and purification, because the main functional groups of bamboo charcoal are mainly carbon-hydrogen bonds and double-carbon bonds, and a small part are hydrogen-oxygen bonds, which can adsorb sulfide, formaldehyde, benzene, phenol or chloroform. Substance, because of its porous nature, it has better adsorption. Bamboo charcoal can be used in many products, and used in toothpaste has many functions, such as whitening, sterilization, deodorization, etc.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/bamboo-toothpaste.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Bamboo Toothpaste</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_bqk71614846153.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/bamboo-toothpaste.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Travel Electric Toothbrush</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_bx5c1614846159.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Children&amp;rsquo;s Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney BOBI Children&amp;rsquo;s Electric Toothbrush uses DuPont&amp;rsquo;s top soft bristles protects the Sensitive and fragile gums of children. ( CE ) European and American certification, produced by Disney&amp;#39;s carefully selected factory, let you use it at ease. Gentle sonic vibration, the most comfortable vibration frequency for children. The cleaning power of an electric toothbrush is related to the vibration speed. When choosing an electric toothbrush, the brush head is an important point. Our bristles are made of DuPont&amp;rsquo;s top soft bristles, don&amp;#39;t worry to use even sensitive teeth. In order to clean each tooth smoothly, the brush head of the electric toothbrush is designed to be smaller than the ordinary toothbrush. This is to avoid the brush head from being unable to brush to the innermost part, and at the same time allow the user to spend more time to brush the teeth. Our brush head perfectly fits the size of your child&amp;#39;s teeth, and it can be easily cleaned regardless of the gap between the teeth or other parts that are difficult to brush. This is a great Electric Toothbrush. There are two choices of blue pattern and pink pattern.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/travel-electric-toothbrush.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Travel Electric Toothbrush</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_bx5c1614846159.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/travel-electric-toothbrush.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Mini Electric Toothbrush</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_6i0k1614846166.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Adult Portable Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney BOBI Portable Electric Toothbrush With IPX7 waterproof function, the whole toothbrush can be filled with water, and the whole body can be rinsed and cleaned in a fully enclosed state, which is convenient and hygienic. Peoney Bobi electric toothbrush is super power-saving, environmentally friendly, non-toxic, and waterproof. It can also clean the tea stains caused by drinking tea and coffee. It is a super-functional Bobi electric toothbrush. An electric toothbrush is a type of toothbrush. It can produce automatic and rapid brush bristles vibration, back and forth or in a rotating manner (the brush head rotates clockwise and counterclockwise alternately) to achieve the effect of cleaning teeth. The toothbrush is powered by a drive motor, which makes the toothbrush produce vibrations at or below the speed of sound. The ultrasonic wave of an ultrasonic toothbrush is produced by piezoelectric crystals. It can also clean the tea stains caused by drinking tea and coffee. It is a super-functional Bobi electric toothbrush. Your teeth need to have one.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/mini-electric-toothbrush.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Mini Electric Toothbrush</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_6i0k1614846166.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/mini-electric-toothbrush.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Portable Sonic Toothbrush</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_qyiv1614846171.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Portable Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney BOBI Portable Electric Toothbrush has RoHS Non-toxic, carefully selected manufacturing materials. Children can use it safety. One button operation, making brushing easier. Robust and non-slip design, not afraid of slipping. One-button switch makes brushing easier. Sturdy and drop-proof, it is still intact when dropped accidentally. Electric toothbrushes remove 38% more plaque than manual toothbrushes, which can effectively clean bacteria between teeth and prevent tooth decay. Let children develop the habit of brushing their teeth from an early age, and have a healthy and bright white teeth. When using an electric toothbrush, it is recommended to brush your teeth in a manner similar to manual brushing but don&amp;rsquo;t use force, and slowly move the toothbrush from one tooth to another for cleaning. In this way, brushing your teeth can be correct and clean. Compared with manual toothbrushes, electric toothbrushes are less susceptible to personal brushing skills. The pink model of Peoney electric toothbrush is PON-68-C, and the colors are blue and pink. The size of the electric toothbrush is 2*2*16.5CM, and the total weight is 35 grams (excluding batteries).</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/portable-sonic-toothbrush.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Portable Sonic Toothbrush</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_qyiv1614846171.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/portable-sonic-toothbrush.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Portable Electric Brush</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_hec31614846176.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bobi Portable Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi Portable Electric Toothbrush. The size of the Bobi Electric toothbrush head is suitable to children&amp;rsquo;s small teeth. Brushing steps are easily and reduce the time and power, when you brushing your teeth. Using the same time to brush your teeth, the vibration effect of an electric toothbrush is better than a manual toothbrush. In addition, an electric toothbrush is used to vibrate the brush head at high speed, which greatly improves the efficiency of brushing. The comfort is also better than the manual one. It is a daily necessities that both adults and children need. The blue model of Peoney electric toothbrush is PON-68-C, and the colors are blue and pink. The size of the electric toothbrush is 2*2*16.5CM, and the total weight is 35 grams (excluding batteries). The standard is equipped with a main body and a brush head. The working principle is sonic vibration 10,000 times per minute. The rated voltage is 1.5V (one AAA battery). The waterproof rating is IPX7, and the warranty period is one year. The standard brush head is the daily brush head. It is a Safe and comfortable electric toothbrush, your children need to have one.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/portable-electric-brush.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Portable Electric Brush</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_hec31614846176.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/portable-electric-brush.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Kids Electric Toothbrush Head</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_ustm1614846182.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Portable Electric Toothbrush Head&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney BOBI portable electric toothbrush head uses DuPont&amp;#39;s top soft bristles, vibrating brush head protects children&amp;#39;s gums. Super cute packaging makes children fall in love with brushing teeth. Made of DuPont soft bristles, soft and delicate, it will not hurt the gums and teeth when brushing your teeth. Please read the instructions carefully before using.&amp;nbsp; The arc design can completely fit the tooth curve. Make brushing more effortless and cleaner. It is the best choice for children&amp;#39;s electric toothbrush heads.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/kids-electric-toothbrush-head.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Kids Electric Toothbrush Head</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_ustm1614846182.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/kids-electric-toothbrush-head.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Kids Toothbrush Head</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_x0gn1614846190.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Kids Electric Toothbrush Head&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi Kids Electric Toothbrush Head is well disassembled and installed, children can replace it by themselves. Replaceable brush head, easy to replace and super convenient.. Peoney Bobi electric toothbrushes are certified by the European Union and use non-toxic plastics. The safety is not affordable and the whole family can use them with peace of mind.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/kids-toothbrush-head.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Kids Toothbrush Head</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_x0gn1614846190.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/kids-toothbrush-head.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Toothbrush Head</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_3s351614846195.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Adult Electric Toothbrush Head&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi Adult Electric Toothbrush Head is sealed packaging, no worrying about safety and hygiene. The delivery speed is fast, and the goods can be quickly obtained after placing the order. RoHS compliance, we strictly select the materials of manufacture, non-toxic formula, no need to worry about the use of adults and children. Children under the age of three, please use with an adult.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/toothbrush-head.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Toothbrush Head</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_3s351614846195.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/toothbrush-head.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Electric Brush Head</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_0bz1614846200.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bobi Adult Electric Toothbrush Head&lt;br /&gt;
Bobi Adult Electric Toothbrush Head is RoHS Non-toxic, carefully selected manufacturing materials. With EU certification, children can use it with peace of mind. Check for obvious damage before each use and do not use if damaged. If your mouth has had surgery in the past two months, please consult your dentist before using. European standard and American standard certification, Disney&amp;#39;s strictly selected factory production, so you can use it at ease.&lt;br /&gt;
The head of the Bobi electric toothbrush weighs about plus or minus eight grams, which is light.&lt;br /&gt;
The exterior color is white, the inner color of the bristles is blue, and the outer ring is white to cover the inner bristles.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-brush-head.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Electric Brush Head</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_0bz1614846200.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-brush-head.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Electric Toothbrush For Adults</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_ztbu1614846206.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Adult Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi Adult Electric Toothbrush has robust and non-slip design, not afraid of slipping. Convenient design reducing much time when you are brushing. Restore your pretty teeth and smile simply. Lightweight design makes brushing effortless. Not only shortens the brushing time, but also restores your brighter smile. Rotating brush head left and right rotating cleaning mode. One operation mode makes brushing your teeth easier and simpler. Anti-slip design, the handle part adopts anti-slip design. The adult model of Peoney electric toothbrush is PON-20SA, and the colors are blue plus gray. The size of the adult electric toothbrush is 2.8*3.6*21 CM, and the total weight is 90 grams (excluding batteries). The standard is equipped with a main body and a brush head. Certified by the European and American regulations, Disney&amp;#39;s carefully selected factory-produced products, so you can use it with more peace of mind. The working principle is sonic rotation 6,000 times per minute. The rated voltage is 3.0V (two AA battery). The waterproof rating is IPX7, and the warranty period is one year.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-toothbrush-for-adults.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Electric Toothbrush For Adults</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_ztbu1614846206.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-toothbrush-for-adults.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Electric Toothbrush Adults</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_2a5g1614846210.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bobi Adult Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi Adult Electric Toothbrush with IPX7 waterproof function, can enter the water. One button operation, making brushing easier.&amp;nbsp; One-button switch makes brushing easier. RoHS non-toxic, carefully selected manufacturing materials. The vibration effect of an electric toothbrush is better than a manual toothbrush. It can clean the tea stains caused by drinking tea and coffee, the most comfortable vibration frequency. The best electric toothbrush to protect and clean your teeth. Owning a Bobi electric toothbrush will keep your teeth clean.&amp;nbsp; The size of the toothbrush head is suitable to adult&amp;rsquo;s teeth. Brushing steps are easily and reduce the time and power, when you brushing your teeth. Using the same time to brush your teeth, the vibration effect of an electric toothbrush is better than a manual toothbrush. Peoney Bobi electric toothbrush is super power-saving, environmentally friendly, non-toxic, and waterproof. It can also clean the tea stains caused by drinking tea and coffee. When choosing an electric toothbrush, the brush head is an important point.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-toothbrush-adults.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Electric Toothbrush Adults</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_2a5g1614846210.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-toothbrush-adults.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Electric Brush For Adults</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_zc371614846216.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi Electric Toothbrush. Through massage and clean method of electric toothbrush, killing bacterial simply. Through massage, it can promote blood circulation in the mouth. Effectively prevent tooth decay and remove much dental plaque than others manual toothbrushes. The vibration massage cleaning mode not only allows bacteria nowhere to hide, but also promotes oral blood circulation through massage. It removes 38% more plaque than a manual toothbrush, effectively preventing tooth decay. The round brush head design allows the vegetable residue or dirt stuck in the gap between the teeth to be removed, and the cleaning angle has no dead ends. Save you from tooth decay. In terms of cleaning, Peoney Bobi electric toothbrushes remove 38% more plaque than manual toothbrushes, and can effectively clean the bacteria between the teeth, thus achieving the effect of preventing tooth decay. In terms of time, we use the same time to calculate the manual toothbrush and the electric toothbrush. We will find that the vibration effect of the electric toothbrush is better than the manual one, and the cleaning effect is better. In terms of comfort, because the BOBI electric toothbrush is a high-speed rotating brush head, it not only promotes blood circulation in the oral cavity, but also has a certain degree of massage effect on the gum tissue.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-brush-for-adults.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Electric Brush For Adults</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_zc371614846216.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-brush-for-adults.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Electric Brush</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_g5y21614846221.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bobi Adult Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
BOBI adult electric toothbrush uses DuPont soft bristles and has certification of European and American specifications ( CE ), RoHS. Through Left and right rotating cleaning mode to achieve the best effect of brushing. In terms of color, electric toothbrushes can effectively reduce tooth stains caused by drinking tea, coffee or some poor oral habits, so that your teeth can restore their original color. Through the vibration massage mode, in the process of cleaning the teeth, it also helps the teeth SPA by the way. Not only the cleaning effect, but also the massage effect. It is an electric toothbrush with multiple functions. RoHs is the abbreviation of the Restriction of the use of certain hazardous substances in electrical and electronic equipment. The standard will be officially implemented on July 1, 2006, and is mainly used to standardize the material and process standards of electrical and electronic products to make it more conducive to human health and environmental protection. The purpose of the standard is to eliminate six substances including lead, mercury, cadmium, hexavalent chromium, polybrominated biphenyls and polybrominated diphenyl ethers in electrical and electronic products, and it specifically stipulates that the content of lead cannot exceed 1%. Customers can use it without a doubt.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-brush.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Electric Brush</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_g5y21614846221.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-brush.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Auto Toothbrush</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_mgd1614846241.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Adult Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi Adult Electric Toothbrush won the charity ambassador certificate in the Chinese Charity Festival in 2019. The Chinese Charity Festival is Taiwan&amp;rsquo;s first festival named after the theme of charity. It aims to build a charity platform and promote the spirit of charity. The activity combines the Chinese Charity Exhibition, the Chinese Leaders Forum, the Chinese Charity Foundation Award and recognition, and the Chinese charity ambassador will give honors. And a series of activities such as the issue of a special issue of the Chinese Charity Festival, successfully highlighting the issues of corporate social responsibility, CSR and charity, and getting attention and discussion by Chinese people around the world.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/auto-toothbrush.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Auto Toothbrush</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_mgd1614846241.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/auto-toothbrush.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Autobrush For Adults</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_fkm91614846247.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bobi Adult Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi Adult Electric Toothbrush has a good shape and good grip, which makes the toothbrush not only good for brushing but also good looking. Please squeeze the right amount of toothpaste on the toothbrush. Please put the toothbrush in your mouth before pressing the power switch. Keep the toothbrush on the surface of the tooth for a few seconds.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/autobrush-for-adults.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Autobrush For Adults</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_fkm91614846247.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/autobrush-for-adults.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Autobrush Adults</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_3d211614846252.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Bobi Adult Rotational Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
The gray and blue design of Peoney Bobi Adult electric toothbrush makes the overall appearance of the toothbrush more fashionable and beautiful. Please move slowly and do not brush hand. Please replace the toothbrush bristles if it is worn. Do not tilt when inserting the toothbrush head. To avoid danger, please keep this product away from baby. Please put this product in a cool and dry place, and avoid direct sunlight and high temperature environment. The standard brush head of the Bobi adult electric toothbrush is a daily-type brush head. The design of the round brush head allows the entire tooth to be completely covered by the toothbrush, and has the cleaning effect of three hundred and sixty degrees. Let bacteria have nowhere to hide.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/autobrush-adults.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Autobrush Adults</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_3d211614846252.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/autobrush-adults.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Auto Toothbrush For Adults</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_fqz51614846257.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney BOBI Adult Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi Adult electric toothbrush pass the EU non-toxic certification, environmental protection and peace of mind. Insist on using high quality and pass strict checks, the purpose is to let consumers feel at ease to use. Don&amp;#39;t worry about eating poison into your stomach. After all, toothbrushes are personal items that you need to use everyday.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/auto-toothbrush-for-adults.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Auto Toothbrush For Adults</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_fqz51614846257.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/auto-toothbrush-for-adults.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Electric Toothbrush For Kids</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_02n11614846262.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Kids Portable Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi Kids Portable Electric Toothbrush. Adhere to the use of all natural non-toxic materials, and pass the dual certification of European and American regulations, quality is guaranteed.&lt;br /&gt;
Bobi &amp;amp; Bomi endorsed PeoneyBobi products that accompany you, ranging from electric toothbrushes for children to electric toothbrushes for adults. They are suitable for families and aim for a beautiful smile.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-toothbrush-for-kids.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Electric Toothbrush For Kids</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_02n11614846262.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-toothbrush-for-kids.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Electric Toothbrush Kids</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_3h7q1614846267.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney BOBI Children Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi Children Electric Toothbrush. The appearance is small and cute, and there is a brand mascot Bobi on the outside. The child couldn&amp;#39;t put it down. Adopt RoHS non-toxic EU certified environmental protection materials, not afraid of children biting with teeth. 10000R/min mild sonic vibration more effectively cleans the bacteria between the teeth to prevent tooth decay.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-toothbrush-kids.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Electric Toothbrush Kids</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_3h7q1614846267.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-toothbrush-kids.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Electric Brush For Kids</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_kymr1614846272.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Children Portable Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi Children Portable Electric Toothbrush. Develop a good habit of brushing their teeth since childhood, and keep toothaches and cavities away from children.&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi Bamboo Charcoal Healthy Toothpaste. In addition to toothbrushes, toothpaste is indispensable for maintaining dental health. Peoney also developed food-grade Bobi Bamboo Charcoal Healthy Toothpaste because it removes chemical abrasives and foams that accumulate toxins. Therefore, it is not afraid of accidentally swallowing by children or family members; the taste of toothpaste will not choke, and it can be used by adults, children or the elderly.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-brush-for-kids.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Electric Brush For Kids</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_kymr1614846272.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-brush-for-kids.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Electric Brush Kids</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_sh51614846277.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Portable Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi Portable Electric Toothbrush. There are two styles and patterns to choose from, regardless of whether boys or girls love them. The reason for choosing an electric toothbrush is that it is more comfortable to use than a manual toothbrush; and the gentle vibration will prevent you from feeling too strong when brushing your teeth, which will cause your hands to feel numb. This electric toothbrush has a closed lid design, so you do not have to worry about the toothbrush being contaminated with bacteria when you go out.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-brush-kids.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Electric Brush Kids</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_sh51614846277.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/electric-brush-kids.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Kids Autobrush</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_gl4l1614846286.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Children Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Children Electric Toothbrush. It is the product development of Peoney Technology Co., Ltd. The initial design was based on the needs of children, so the Bobi portable electric toothbrush was introduced, which is easy for children to use.&lt;br /&gt;
Later, electric toothbrushes that are suitable for the whole family to carry and use have been developed one after another, so that adults and children in family can smile beautifully.&lt;br /&gt;
&amp;nbsp;</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/kids-autobrush.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Kids Autobrush</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_gl4l1614846286.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/kids-autobrush.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Autobrush Kids</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_vfjm1614846293.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Bobi Kids Portable Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi kid&amp;rsquo;s Portable Electric Toothbrush. Mascot Bomi was born in West Central District,Tainan City, Taiwan in December 2018. She usually stands guard on the 2nd floor of Asakusa Youth Xintiandi, West Gate, No. 26, Section 3, Guohua Street, a famous snack street in Tainan,Taiwan. With many years of experience in the design and development of IC applications, the person in charge has developed a high-quality electric toothbrush that can be used by adults and children.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/autobrush-kids.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Autobrush Kids</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_vfjm1614846293.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/autobrush-kids.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Autobrush For Kids</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_ibo1614846301.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Kids Portable Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Bobi kid&amp;rsquo;s Portable Electric Toothbrush. The main team of Peoney comes from the senior consumer IC electronic application team in Hsinchu Science Park. It has strong and mature electronic technology strength, combined with Disney&amp;rsquo;s electric toothbrush foundry cooperation, and has a high-level manufacturing process and dust-free ISO certified factory for clean production.&lt;br /&gt;
The full range of products are sold on many Taiwan online shopping platforms such as PChome, Shopee, Post Mall, and official websites.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/autobrush-for-kids.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Autobrush For Kids</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_ibo1614846301.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/autobrush-for-kids.html</link>	     </image>     </item>         <item>	     <title>Auto Toothbrush For Kids</title>	     <description>&lt;img src='productpic/ps_q2ho1614846310.jpg' /&gt;&lt;br&gt;Peoney Children Portable Electric Toothbrush&lt;br /&gt;
Peoney Children Portable Electric Toothbrush. The main team of Peoney comes from the senior consumer IC electronic application team in Hsinchu Science Park. It has strong and mature electronic technology strength, combined with Disney&amp;rsquo;s electric toothbrush foundry cooperation, and has a high-level manufacturing process and dust-free ISO certified factory for clean production.&lt;br /&gt;
The full range of products are sold on many Taiwan online shopping platforms such as PChome,Shopee, Post Mall, and official websites.</description>	      <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/auto-toothbrush-for-kids.html</link>		     <image>	         <title>Auto Toothbrush For Kids</title>		     <url>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/productpic/ps_q2ho1614846310.jpg</url>		     <link>http://www.electrictoothbrush.org/auto-toothbrush-for-kids.html</link>	     </image>     </item>    	 </channel></rss>